<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[APAP_OVERVIEW]]></title><description><![CDATA[Obsidian digital garden]]></description><link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link><image><url>site-lib/media/favicon.png</url><title>APAP_OVERVIEW</title><link></link></image><generator>Webpage HTML Export plugin for Obsidian</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:30:45 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="site-lib/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:30:40 GMT</pubDate><ttl>60</ttl><dc:creator></dc:creator><item><title><![CDATA[CHARACTERS]]></title><description><![CDATA[The player KARacter. A diffuse personality. Humble, but lost and gullible. Doesn't feel good about performing morally questionable actions, but still does it out of naivety, fear of conflict. Trying to achieve good things by doing bad things.
Trying to accommodate his inner voice of an evil, manipulative, drowned kid, and at the same time maintain a functional everyday life<img alt="_IMAGES/KAR.png" src="_images/kar.png" target="_self" style="width: 216px; max-width: 100%;">The Other Boy. Mostly stays in KARs closet during the days and gives KAR chores. TOB is a figment of KAR's imagination. TOB claims to be KAR's childhood friend who supposedly fell and drowned and disappeared into a sewer sometime in the nineties. TOB also claims that KAR let this happen. But that he is no longer angry with KAR as they were "just kids" at the time of the incident. TOB understands, however, that this has led to KAR feeling like a very bad person. TOB wants to help KAR become a better person. To achieve this, KAR needs to do exactly what TOB asks.
TOB hates sunlight
TOB hates pets
TOB hates disobedience
TOB smells rotten
TOB is wet
<br><img alt="_IMAGES/TOB.png" src="_images/tob.png" target="_self" style="width: 156px; max-width: 100%;">Sebastian Sparre. Neighbor. Comes visiting sometimes. Demanding
Unpredictable
Kleptomaniac
Generous (sometimes)
Drug addict
Animal lover
Asks for: pet related stuff, find things he claims to have lost (often pets and valuable things), borrow anything of value
Helps with: drops bags of "borrowed" stuff at KAR sometimes, brings gifts when he is "happy", a walking medicine cabinet<br><img alt="_IMAGES/SEB.png" src="_images/seb.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Karl-Kaj Algren. Former music school teacher. Now early retired, local troubadour (according to himself famous). A rather likeable neighbor, whose delusions of grandeur mixed with self-pity can get on one's nerves.
Attention-seeking
Self-pity
Asks for: Booze, cigarettes, guitar strings, an audience
Helps with: Calm things down with music<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/KALKAN.png" src="_images/kalkan.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">
Siv Jakobsson is stuck in the spiritual world. Difficult to communicate with. Have strange wishes and ideas about most things. Love shiny stones, rat tails and bird claws etc. Siv gets offended easily.
Lives with MAN and owns three small dogs (pompoms).
Asks for: Weird objects to make totem necklaces which gives spiritual strength,
Helps with: spiritual some what unreliable strength<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/SIV.png" src="_images/siv.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Oliver Brovic. Nervous and cryptic gentleman. Building something very advanced in his apartment.
Asking for: strange books, technical components, pills, coffee
Helps with: solving riddles<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/OLI.png" src="_images/oli.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">A little scared boy in the shape of a very large man. Living with Siv and her three pompoms. Haven't found any other asset in life than overreaction and excessive violence.<br><img alt="_IMAGES/MAN.png" src="_images/man.png" target="_self" style="width: 372px; max-width: 100%;">Ann Birgersson. Mother of the two uncontrollable kids ravaging the neighborhood. Nurse on sick leave.
Asks for: Her kids, cigarettes, sleeping pills, candy, kid-size cages
Helps with: some nursing care, medical equipment (medkit)<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/ANN.png" src="_images/ann.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Jon Berglund is a broker/banker who lives on the verge of the collapse. Hysterically nice person tries to maintain the appearance of normality, even if everything is already lost. He is seriously concerned that people think he is wierd and poor. This takes up all his time.
Becoming increasingly confused. He's a ticking bomb.<br><img alt="_IMAGES/BKM.png" src="_images/bkm.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Ali Bilal. Heart-sick Syrian exile poet. Sympathetic. Ali is terrorized by neighbor (he wont tell who). Would like to stay in KAR's apartment and write The Poem. May have cardiac arrest by barking dogs and other sudden loud noises.
Asks for: beta blockers, animals to pet, cigarettes, coffee, a locked room (peace and quiet)
Helps with: Talking to ABI calms KAR, KAR needs the finished Poem for some reason
//todo: reason<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/ABI.png" src="_images/abi.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Jan is a property manager. He is taciturn and very duty driven. If something needs to be done, it will be done. He has the main key and is happy to check an extra time if KAR's kitchen fan is working properly. Likes to be invited to coffee and preferably some snacks. Dislikes messy tenants. Be sure to be properly dressed when he comes to visit (anytime). Gets grumpy easily. Far-sighted.
Asks for: coffee, snacks and good behavior
Helps with: property problems (if not grumpy)<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/JAN.png" src="_images/jan.png" target="_self" style="width: 312px; max-width: 100%;">Daniel. The property manager's brain-damaged son. Claw-fingered and messy. Hurts pets and some times hugging them til death. Joins Jan to work sometimes. The frequency tends to correlate with the level of Jan's grumpiness.
Asks for: a spanking
Helps with: nothing at all<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/JANJ.png" src="_images/janj.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Pranksters who buzz on KARs doorbell run away / run in and more. During the course of the game, the smoker throws his apartment's contents out into the yard, blocking the way between rooms. The first time KAR encounters the smoker is in the Dream Land when he wants to set fire to the swan.
Asks for: a light / fire
Helps with: escalates the last stage of blockage (burning household pile) in the yard<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/SMOKER.png" src="_images/smoker.png" target="_self" style="width: 272px; max-width: 100%;">The builder is a neighbor who during the game builds a wooden wall between the rooms in the yard. The builder has had a revelation about walls needing to be built wherever there are none. The first time KAR meets the Builder is on the Owl path in the Dream World, where his building ladders and wooden houses for the visitors of the owl.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/BUILDER.png" src="_images/builder.png" target="_self" style="width: 272px; max-width: 100%;">Cryers are schoolchildren who appear in the hallway outside KAR's apartment. They may have useful things in their backpack, but it's not always worth the risk of trying to investigate.<br><img alt="_IMAGES/CRYER.png" src="_images/cryer.png" target="_self" style="width: 372px; max-width: 100%;">Keeps track of KAR's doings. A neighbor that KAR never meets in a person in an awake state. He informs KAR about important things through anonymous notes in the letter box. In the Dream World, he manifests himself as the bureaucrat. A helpful, but also zealous gentleman.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/ADMIN.png" src="_images/admin.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Food delivery with three personalities. Moves around in the corridor, looking for the right door, often at various stages of confused state (depending on active personality).<br><img alt="_IMAGES/DELI.png" src="_images/deli.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">
The food delivery is also a business owner in The Dream Land. It is not always easy to do business with three psychotic traders at the same time.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/STOREOWNER.png" src="_images/storeowner.png" target="_self" style="width: 372px; max-width: 100%;">(Dream Animal)
The dream fox seems to be a trigger happy righteous man. A kind of sheriff of the dream world? He hates big and little fuckers for understandable reasons and needs KAR's help.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/FOX.png" src="_images/fox.png" target="_self" style="width: 196px; max-width: 100%;">The little fox is kidnapped by Big Fucker because of his tourette syndrome.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/lilFOX.png" src="_images/lilfox.png" target="_self" style="width: 156px; max-width: 100%;">(Dream Animal)
Not all owls smart. Or even make sense. No matter what KAR needs to do what the this weirdo is asking.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/OWL.png" src="_images/owl.png" target="_self" style="width: 412px; max-width: 100%;">(Dream Animal)
Even tigers can become desperate for friendship. Captures and cages the animals of the forest to ensure that they remain with her. Best friends forever!<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/TIGR.png" src="_images/tigr.png" target="_self" style="width: 472px; max-width: 100%;">(Dream Animal)
A swan in a lake in a dream world.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/SWAN.png" src="_images/swan.png" target="_self" style="width: 272px; max-width: 100%;">Had enough of Little Fox's constant insults.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/BFU.png" src="_images/bfu.png" target="_self">She ok? She needs help getting away from her terrorizing husband.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/MrsOCTO.png" src="_images/mrsocto.png" target="_self" style="width: 196px; max-width: 100%;">Obnoxious, unsympathetic octopus man. Makes an extremely annoyed noise when he is displeased. Make him shut up somehow.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/OCTO.png" src="_images/octo.png" target="_self" style="width: 572px; max-width: 100%;">Gives and takes.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/YONI.png" src="_images/yoni.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;">The almighty.<br>
<img alt="_IMAGES/TURD.png" src="_images/turd.png" target="_self" style="width: 128px; max-width: 100%;">]]></description><link>characters.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHARACTERS.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 23:29:09 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/kar.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/kar.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MECHANICS]]></title><description><![CDATA[The main game loop of the game is a day for KAR.
KAR wakes up in the apartment, uses up their action points and falls asleep and goes to the Dream Land.
When KAR goes back to bed, or dies, in the Dream Land they wake up on the following day.
Every new day triggers one or more events that KAR needs to deal with.
During the second and third chapters of the game, TOB also asks KAR to perform chores for him. If KAR refuses or forgets, TOB punishes him.
After enough chores, The Egg cracks open and spawns a new KAR, TOB brings the old KAR down into the sewers and the game starts over.
Every new KAR is slightly worse off than the last, making the game a little bit harder with every loop.
If KAR dies, the game starts over with a fresh KAR. If KAR manages to get down into the Sewers without TOB, he'll break the cycle and beat the game.
To get into the Sewers, KAR needs to obtain 4 keys from the Dream Animals.
The keys unlock doors in the Corridor where KAR finds objects that are used to unblock the rooms in the Yard. there are 3 types of events, TOB, Triggered and Visitor. TOB:
Every morning when KAR wakes up, a random TOB event is triggered. Triggered:
Triggered events are most often triggered when KAR wakes up in the morning, or at a set time after KAR does some certain action.Visitor:
Every few days, a random visitor event gets triggered. KAR has a limited amount of Action Points (AP).
When KAR runs out of AP, KAR falls asleep and goes to Dream Land.
Sleeping restores some AP.
Doing chores for TOB may reward candies that restore AP. The game as a whole is divided up into 3 chapters.
See CHAPTERS for more detail. ]]></description><link>mechanics.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">MECHANICS.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:36:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CHAPTER 1]]></title><description><![CDATA[Before TOB moves in.
Think of this as a tutorial chapter.
KAR just needs to take care of himself, eat, shit and sleep.
KAR finds a suitcase in the closet with a stuffed animal in it.
Something snaps inside of KAR when he picks it up, holding it physically hurts.
KAR needs to get rid of it.
Unless he flushes it down the toilet, the stuffed always animal reappears in the suitcase in The Closet.
Unless he flushes it down, it starts whispering to him, cryptically instructing him to flush it down the toilet.
By flushing the stuffed animal, KAR unknowingly invites TOB to move in.
This starts Chapter 2.Early in Chapter One, KAR receives a note through the mail box that says something very cryptic that alludes to the hidden goal (The Real End) of the game.]]></description><link>chapters/chapter-1.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHAPTERS/CHAPTER 1.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:35:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OBJECTS]]></title><description><![CDATA[Descriptions of some significant objects in the game. Stuffed Dream Animals:
Stuffed toy versions of the 4 Dream Animals. One is found in the beginning of the game in The Closet and needs to be flushed down the toilet.
If KAR finds another plush, it can be given to TOB, letting KAR off the hook from his chores that day. AP-candy:
Candy in different flavors that restore some AP.
Can be used to buy stuff from the Shop Keep.
Can have different effects. Blender
A container that mixes things. Used to make sewer food for TOB. Flowers
Watering flowers makes KAR feel good.TV]]></description><link>objects.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">OBJECTS.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:33:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CHAPTER 2]]></title><description><![CDATA[In Chapter 2 TOB moves in to the closet and starts giving KAR chores.
When TOB moves in, he takes away half of KAR's life force (AP) and rewards AP-restoring-candy for completing chores for him.
KAR needs to take care of himself and also do what TOB asks of him from now on, or else.
Every day, TOB is hungry and asks KAR to feed him.
In Chapter 2 when KAR goes to sleep he travels to Dream Land. TOB is hungry every day when KAR wakes up.
TOB gives KAR a baby bottle, to be filled up and handed back.
TOB accepts his sewer food in any container (an empty can, wine bottle, or a rag will do), but will only reward AP-candy if he gets fed properly with a closed Baby Bottle.
Sewer Food is made by mixing a Sewer Ball in a Blender.
Sewer Balls can be fished up out of the toilet, new ones spawn at set intervals.
On some days TOB has got cravings for something extra. KAR simply needs to add that extra ingredient to the blender before mixing. recipe ideas:
sewer ball + meat = Meaty Sewer Stew
sewer ball + fruit = Fermented Sewer Fruit
sewer ball + soil = Earthen Sewer Mash
sewer ball + something rotten = Putrid Sewer Slop
sewer ball + alcohol = Distilled Sewer Brew
sewer ball + small animal = Protein Sewer Ration
sewer ball + bones = Calcified Sewer Stock
sewer ball + pills = Medicinal Sewer Paste
sewer ball + dream goat milk = Somnolent Sewer ShakeTOB wants to expand the closet in size and needs some tools for it.
Over time the closet turns into a garden of sorts. Quest 1:
TOB asks for a crowbar.
The day after giving TOB the crowbar, TOB has broken up the floor in the closet and the quest line continues. Quest 2:
TOB asks for enough soil to fill the hole in the ground. He gives KAR a shovel and hints:
"There's plenty of soil in your dreams."
Next time KAR enters the closet after giving TOB the soil, TOB has filled the hole in the ground with soil and the quest line continues. Quest 3:
TOB asks for a "Dream Seed".
KAR needs to go to The Yoni in Dream Land to get the Dream Seed for planting The Tree of Life in the closet. Quest 4:
Fertilizer is needed for the planted Dream Seed.
Note: any type of poop will do. Quest 5:
KAR water needs to water the Dream Seed.
Note: Water needs to be brought in a container of some kind. A wet rag will do.
After being fertilized and watered, the Tree of Life starts growing. It needs to grow big enough to produce fruit.
While the tree is growing, TOB asks for more soil to grow the garden plot more.
Once the tree bears fruit, KAR can take it and eat it, which progresses the quest line. Quest 6:
The Egg
After eating the fruit, KAR's stomache bloats up and the morning after he wakes up with a pulsating egg-like seed next to him in bed.
After planting the Egg Seed in a free plot of soil in The Garden, the questline for Chapter 2 is complete. ]]></description><link>chapters/chapter-2.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHAPTERS/CHAPTER 2.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:11:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TOB_EVENTS]]></title><description><![CDATA[When KAR wakes up every morning, TOB has done something in the apartment. Recurring event. TOB demands food (blended in the blender) consisting of yummy sewage balls (from toilet) or regular food impregnated with sewage water every day. If he doesn't have his daily ration of sewage smoothie, he becomes ill-tempered and uncooperative.A satisfied TOB is rare. A satisfied TOB leaves KAR mostly alone. But it happens, if TOB is exceptionally satisfied, that he does nice things in the apartment while KAR asleep.
watering flowers
picking up trash / cleaning
stocking up on food
decorating
make breakfast for KAR
leaving gifts
KAR can't open some doors in the apartment. They are nailed shut.
KAR needs to find a tool to pull out the nails in order to open the nailed doors.All the food is eaten / ruined / pissed on / flushed down / thrown out.
KAR needs to find new food.A malicious TOB can go wild with the scissors while KARs asleep
plants
clothes
books
posters
pillows
tablecloths
rugs
pets
Someone has broken all the glass bottles in the apartment.
KAR needs to clean up before someone gets hurt.KAR wakes up to discover a room filled with dead kittens.
A malicious TOB combined with possession of kittens is an unfortunate combination.KAR wakes up to find his pet killed.
A malicious TOB combined with possession of a beloved pet is an unfortunate combination.Malicious TOB wakes KAR up in the middle of the night in various unpleasant ways:
suffocates him pees on him
hits him with a hammer
attempts to saw off limbs
applies the AP suction machine
etc.
Disturbs KAR's sleep and thus his presence in the dream world.
Requires a really ill-tempered TOB. KAR is awakened by TOB hitting him in the face with a hammer, resulting in him losing all his teeth. KAR can now only eat liquid food unless he figures out a way to put his teeth back in.KAR can't sleep because something won´t stop whining in the yard. If KAR looks out, he might see a strange creature (from the sewers, calling out to TOB?) staring up at him and whining. Unless KAR finds a way to make it go away, there will be more creatures the next night (the same thing if he tries to ignore it).KAR's most intimate secrets have been written across the walls of the apartment with what appears to be feces. KAR needs to get the mess removed before anyone (worst case, the property manager) sees it, and to get peace of mind.TOB likes to draw strange symbols and illustrations on the apartment walls. This makes KAR really uncomfortable. KAR needs to get the mess removed before anyone (worst case, the property manager) sees it, and to get peace of mind.Someone has built a rudimentary fireplace out of bricks, broken up floorboards, and butchered a wooden chair and some kind of animal somewhere in the apartment. KAR needs to get the mess removed before anyone (worst case, the property manager) sees it, and to get peace of mind.KAR suspects that someone has tampered with the food. Does KAR dare to eat it?
KAR needs to find new food.Piles of entrails makes life miserable for KAR.
KAR needs to get the mess removed before anyone (worst case, the property manager) sees it, and to get peace of mind. KAR wakes up with horrible stomach pains (TOB has offered KAR something strange to eat when KAR is starving?). Something wants to come out. KAR urgently needs to self-medicate with hard liquor to kill what is trying to grow big and powerful in his stomach.KAR wakes up with his skull sawed open. His brain is missing and the scalp is on the floor next to the bed. KAR cannot interact and can only drag himself around the apartment like a drooling zombie. Get back into bed and guide the brain back to KAR's head from its hiding place.An eye sits on the floor, staring at KAR.
It grows over a few days before turning into a black hole that sucks nearby objects into it.TOB has left a handfull of small dead animals strewn around the apartment. The Plant is present and KAR hasn't taken care of it (watered it).
Eats small animals such as dogs, cats, birds if they get too close.
If not fed, eventually breaks free and starts walking around using it's roots as legs. KAR finds one of the neighbor's children dead in the apartment.KAR becomes invisible.
KAR can't inspect themself. KAR's shadow is acting strange.
todo: event needs more fleshing out. KAR's reflection is acting strange.
Breaking the mirror ends the event. KAR wakes up to a clone of himself in the apartment.
The clone follows KAR around.
It asks annoying questions.
"Is this it?"
"Is this who I am?"
"Am I you?"
"Are you me?"
todo: how do you get rid of the clone in a responsible way?Something is making noise from the ventilations.
Opening the vent to figure out what it is ends the event.
The more days it is present and not taken care of, the larger the thing hiding inside. A small hole appears in a wall or the floor.
KAR can peak inside to find something. KAR finds one half of his beloved pet. Where is the other part?Everything is heavier than usual.
Picking up anything costs AP.
Getting out of bed, off the couch etc costs 2x AP. A locked box is found in the apartment.
KAR needs a key to open it. Anything KAR touches today immediately starts decaying/molding and spawns flies.KAR has no skin and bleeds all the time.
Very sensitive to touch, obviously. ]]></description><link>events/tob_events.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVENTS/TOB_EVENTS.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 17:04:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[INDEX]]></title><description><![CDATA[<a data-href="CHARACTERS" href="characters.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CHARACTERS</a><br>
<a data-href="CREATURES" href="creatures.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CREATURES</a><br>
<a data-href="LOCATIONS" href="locations.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">LOCATIONS</a><br>
<a data-href="MECHANICS" href="mechanics.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">MECHANICS</a><br>
<a data-href="OBJECTS" href="objects.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">OBJECTS</a>CHAPTERS<br>
<a data-href="CHAPTER 1" href="chapters/chapter-1.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CHAPTER 1</a><br>
<a data-href="CHAPTER 2" href="chapters/chapter-2.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CHAPTER 2</a><br>
<a data-href="CHAPTER 3" href="chapters/chapter-3.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CHAPTER 3</a>EVENTS<br>
<a data-href="TOB_EVENTS" href="events/tob_events.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">TOB_EVENTS</a><br>
<a data-href="TRIGGER_EVENTS" href="events/trigger_events.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">TRIGGER_EVENTS</a><br>
<a data-href="VISITOR_EVENTS" href="events/visitor_events.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">VISITOR_EVENTS</a>LOCATION DETAILS<br>
<a data-href="CLOSET" href="location-details/closet.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">CLOSET</a><br>
<a data-href="DREAM LAND" href="location-details/dream-land.html" class="internal-link" target="_self" rel="noopener nofollow">DREAM LAND</a>]]></description><link>index.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">INDEX.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:54:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CLOSET]]></title><description><![CDATA[TOB lives in KAR's closet.
Over time, the closet expands in size and contains plots of dirt where KAR is sometimes allowed to plant seeds.
<img alt="closet.png" src="_images/closet.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;">As part of Chapter 2, TOB makes KAR plant The Egg in The Garden.
In Chapter 3, taking care of The Egg is a central theme.
The Egg grows a new KAR.
When the egg hatches, TOB brings the old KAR down into the sewers and the game starts again with the new one.<br>
<img alt="KARnEGG.png" src="_images/karnegg.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;"><br><img alt="TREE_OF_LIFE.png" src="_images/tree_of_life.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;">]]></description><link>location-details/closet.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOCATION DETAILS/CLOSET.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 15:29:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/closet.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/closet.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[VISITOR_EVENTS]]></title><description><![CDATA[A neighbor or something visits KAR. A bird flies in through an open or broken window.
It might bring something in its claws.
They lose feathers and empty their bowels on the floor if they are startled.A fish peaks out of the toilet.
It might bring something from the sewers.
KAR can talk to the fish.Neighbor gives KAR their pet, to take care of for a few days.
Neighbor willll come back to pick it up, and gives a reward if KAR manages to give the dog back in one piece. ANN hands over her kid (kid may be familiar from previous events). This is no big issue if KAR is in balance and prepared with vhs movies, popcorn and spiked soda. If not, it can be all the more problematic.A random neighbor comes by and asks for an item they are missing for various reasons.KAR comes across a box filled with dead or living kittens.KAR comes across a bag with dead or living kittens.KID rings the door and slips into KARs apartment.
Screams and tosses things around if KAR gets close to them.
KAR needs to pick up KID and toss em out in the hallway again. A strange kid comes to visit. The kid follows KAR and stares at him without saying anything. This makes KAR uncomfortable.A kid with duct tape wrapped around his head bangs on door. It runs into the apartment if KAR opens. If KAR removes the tape, the child starts screaming hysterically and refuses to stop, or bounces around of joy and gives KAR a bag of mixed AP candy (small ones). If KAR does not help the child, the child collapses on the floor and suffocates.A hurt child rings the doorbell. He asks for help and claims to have been attacked by a stray dog in the hallway. If KAR helps the child (bandages it), KAR receives a special sausage that the child has picked up in the hallway. The sausage may come in handy in the future.A kid rings the doorbell and says that he has been thrown out by his mean parents because they claim he ate an entire package of cornflakes. If KAR has a package of cornflakes and gives it to the kid, the kid will laugh and run away. If KAR does not give a package, the child get angry, pee on the floor and threaten that his mother will come and stab KAR in both eyes with a knife. And maybe she will.KAR for a visit from a bloated cat. It seems pregnant.
It can give birth to between 5 and 15 kittens. Kittens are cute and precious. However, some cats are bloated for reasons other than pregnancy. Keep or get rid of?Dogs eat some really disgusting things that can cause their intestines to produce corrosive feces and unhealthy gases. But dogs can get pregnant too. Puppies are cute and precious.SIV's dogs can run around in the hallway and create a havoc and are happy to run into KAR's apartment if he opens the door at the wrong moment. They bark, bite and poop constantly.
Get them out, but be careful: If anything happens to these little shitheads, Siv and Man will make KAR's life even more miserable.Pompoms have very sensitive stomachs. If they happen to eat anything other than dog food, they will explode. Creates a sloppy mess and angry owners.Someone has placed a severed pig's head outside KAR's front door.Neighbor slips a note in KARs mailbox. Often containing nonsense or threats, but sometimes also useful information.Recurring event, where SEB comes by. SEB is either chaotic (high/drunk) or calm and quite likeable (somewhat sober). If he is chaotic, he behaves irrationally: picks up things, drops things (a plastic bag with random things he took from other neighbors), talks incoherently, has mood swings, leaves the front door open, etc. The risk, however, is that if SEB comes back before he sobers up to pick up his things. He will not be happy if they are gone.When sober, he is more of a businessman who likes to barter with KAR. For example, various useful pills for random saleable items. SEB won't come visit KAR sober if he's mad at him.Recurring event. Kalkan is a lonely man who craves attention. He likes to knock on KAR's door in the hope of being invited for a drink or more and get the opportunity perform his his own composed song to an audience.He is very interested in hearing what KAR thinks of the song and always thinks KAR hates it, no matter what KAR says to him.
Kalkan tends to get inappropriately emotional, wants to be hugged and refuses to leave (sieges the couch).Kalkan has a CD of his music that he wants to sell to KAR.Kalkan is talking about a video recording that contains evidence of him performing at a local pub thirteen years ago. But he can't find it anywhere.Kalkan claims that little furry demons gnaw on the strings of his guitar when he sleeps. Some nights even on his vocal cords.
A big reason why he is afraid to sleep alone.How does KAR get rid of Kalkan?Recurring event. She has recurring visions that tell her about KAR's fate, which she of course needs to tell KAR about. SIV wants special dream stones, of which she makes spiritually strengthening necklaces and such.SIV gets upset if KAR doesn't give here new dream stones when she asks for them.
She can try to give KAR cursed tokens or send MAN to correct KAR's behavior.If KAR manages to lure Mr Octo to the dream world by having the Octoman (1971) movie on VHS in his possession:
Mr Octo besieges KAR's couch and demands that the same movie be played 24/7 for three days. If KAR fails to rewind the movie in time, Mr Octo gets angry and makes the living room a no-go zone for KAR. Mr. Octo likes to eat pizza and pets.If KAR upsets SIV, MAN will come to visit on her behalf. He will calmly explain what KAR needs to do to make things right. If KAR doesn't do as he says, MAN will be a pain to deal with in the future.MAN doesn't like KAR giving SIV stones. She doesn't talk about anything else and is acting weirder than usual. The stones are obviously cursed, according to MAN.MAN can also appear KAR fails to evict The Pompoms from the apartment in a gentle manner. In this situation, he is the opposite of calm.MAN is capable of breaking down KAR's front door if really enraged. JON is convinced that there is another half-naked person running around the house, imitating him, behaving badly and spreading lies. Which is not at all strange, according to Jon, as people who have not succeeded in life have a hard time dealing with the fact that he has it. They are jealous.JON wants KAR to keep his eyes open and let him know if he encounters the impersonator.When KAR encounters the "impersonator", who really looks just like a half-naked, fucked up JON (it is), he is happy to tell you what he thinks about the real JON, as well as share various secrets about him.]]></description><link>events/visitor_events.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVENTS/VISITOR_EVENTS.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CREATURES]]></title><description><![CDATA[One of SEBs pets. A fluff motion detector.
<img alt="SHRIMP.png" src="_images/shrimp.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">One of SEBs pets. Nibbly and always hungry.<br>
<img alt="FRANK.png" src="_images/frank.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Sivs barking terror crew.<br>
<img alt="POMS.png" src="_images/poms.png" target="_self" style="width: 312px; max-width: 100%;">Compressed cuteness. Easy to step on, so watch out.<br>
<img alt="KITTENS.png" src="_images/kittens.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Uncontrollable love-guzzlers and carpet peeers.<br>
<img alt="CATS.png" src="_images/cats.png" target="_self" style="width: 312px; max-width: 100%;">Filthy, biting, antisocial pests. Attracted to trash and filth.<br>
<img alt="RATS.png" src="_images/rats.png" target="_self" style="width: 372px; max-width: 100%;">Curious, loud and thieving.<br>
<img alt="CROWS.png" src="_images/crows.png" target="_self" style="width: 312px; max-width: 100%;">Annoying little dudes that can be helpful in the dream world or not.<br>
<img alt="POINTERS.png" src="_images/pointers.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">Troublemakers from the Dream World that seem to exist to annoy the entire universe. Completely ignores all rules of conduct about what is real and what is not.<br>
<img alt="LFU.png" src="_images/lfu.png" target="_self" style="width: 372px; max-width: 100%;">Fish from the dream world. Yummy, but also sucky.<br>
<img alt="FISHES.png" src="_images/fishes.png" target="_self" style="width: 296px; max-width: 100%;">What happens if a dog takes a little to much liking to a rat, or the reverse?<br>
<img alt="ROGS.png" src="_images/rogs.png" target="_self" style="width: 456px; max-width: 100%;">Very very yummy dream goat milk. Has a soporific effect, especially on drowned, narcissistic ghost kids. Be careful, goats have a short fuse.<br><img alt="GOATS.png" src="_images/goats.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;">The nird bird is always surprised and expresses it. Its sound can wake you up when you least want it.<br>
<img alt="NIRD.png" src="_images/nird.png" target="_self" style="width: 256px; max-width: 100%;">]]></description><link>creatures.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CREATURES.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:01:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/shrimp.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/shrimp.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TRIGGER_EVENTS]]></title><description><![CDATA[Based on KARs actions, an event can trigger in the apartment.
They can trigger after a set time, or the next morning as KAR wakes up.
Can be thought of as "consequences" rather than events I guess. Running out of coffee is a major problem, especially when it is required to keep special visitors happy. KAR needs to find ways to get hold of coffee package.
Neighbors' delivered grocery bags in the hallway
Barter with neighbor
Dropped food delivery bags
Buy from Shop Keep
Growing coffee beans in the dream garden?
Too many flies in the apartment lures Toads out of the toilet.
The toad is very voracious and disgusting and is quickly growing problematically large unless KAR puts a stop to it.If KAR falls asleep with the front door open (can be left open for various reasons), it can lead to one thing or another.
In this case, a creature (or kids) has snuck in and found a hiding place in the apartment.
spots: cabinets, bathtub, rug, sofa cushion, piles of trash and such
Something is hiding under the rug. Stomp on or investigate?
A moan is heard from a hiding place. A gurgling sound is heard from a hiding place.
Cabinet door is ajar
A burglary has occurred and various items have been stolen.Knocks on the wall when KAR moves or interacts.
Someone behind the wall thinks KAR has been running around and slamming doors too much.
KAR needs to stay quiet for a longer period of time to silence the knocking.Too much waste/garbage in one room creates the conditions for a rat colony to make itself at home. There are more rats every day. KAR needs to stop this by removing the trash and wipe out the colony.KAR has left something stinky laying around. The smell affects the entire room / container.
Triggers the next morning. The Shrimp can get stuck in a state where she can't stop barking. This might be triggered by too many visitors and noisy neighbors, noise from the yard, etc. If KAR doesn't manage to calm her down, she will bounce around and bark until she shits herself and collapsesSudden noises can cause The Shrimp to start shaking uncontrollably. KAR needs to calm her down or she will shake until she shits herself and collapsesRequires upset neighbor. An object flies through the window in the middle of the night.KAR has had an allergic reaction after eating an apple (random thing / playthrough?) and is itching badly. KAR needs to find relief before he tears off his skin.If, for example, KAR cannot stop scratching due to severe itching.
KAR has no skin and bleeds all the time.
Very sensitive to touch, obviously.
KAR needs to get some new skin.Untreated rat bites can cause blood poisoning that causes KAR's limbs to rot. KAR needs to act before the rot reaches the heart.KAR ate something bad and gets worms. KAR gets hungry faster and get less positive effects from eating. KAR has made the property manager unhappy.
All water is turned off in the apartment for the entire day.KAR has made the property manager unhappy.
The power is turned off in the apartment for the entire day. KAR has made the property manager unhappy.
It's, like, really warm the entire day.
KAR sweats a lot. Stay hydrated, friend. KAR ate something bad and gets diarrhea.
KAR's stomach will increasingly terrorize KAR in the coming days if KAR does not find a way to cure it, or at least some way to gain control of the situation.KAR left a seed or fruit with seeds somewhere and now it's taken root and started growing from under the floorboards. If KAR has a crowbar, he can remove the floorboard and investigate the root of the plant that can be useful as an smoothie ingredient.A floorboard in the living room creaks when you step on it. If KAR has a crowbar, he can remove the floorboard and investigate. May or may not offer a reward.KAR touches a dead animal that's been laying around for too long and contracts a strange disease.
//todo: effects?KAR hears a fight outside in the hallway. If KAR goes out when it is quiet, he may find
pools of blood, teeth, hair
body parts
bag with items
weapons / tools
If KAR goes out before it is quiet, KAR will also be attacked.
Requires upset neighbor.
A police officer rings the doorbell and explains that they have received a report of concern and asks if everything is okay.A police officer knocks on the door and explains that they have received a report of concern and asks if everything is okay.A police officer bangs on the door and demands that KAR open. Immediately.KAR didn't flush the toilet, or left something in the sink.
And now it's clogged up. Flushing the things down the toilet may be convenient, but may also clog it.Interesting mushrooms can start growing in old turds if left laying around.
Ingredient for cleansing smoothie (to empty oneself of problematic content)?An untreated wound might get a fungal infection. Not particularly healthy, but these kind of special mushrooms can be useful.KAR has been exposed to the cold and wakes up with a strange cough. KAR's lungs will terrorize KAR increasingly in the coming days if KAR doesn't find a way to cure it (unless he wants to meet his lungs in person). May annoy neighbors.]]></description><link>events/trigger_events.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">EVENTS/TRIGGER_EVENTS.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:01:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[CHAPTER 3]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Egg is growing.
Dream Land expands in size, paths are now available to try to visit the Dream Animals.
KAR needs to water and take care of The Egg everyday, while also feeding TOB and himself.
If The Egg hatches, TOB pulls the old KAR down into the sewers and the game starts over with the newly hatched KAR.
To break the cycle, KAR needs to: kill New KAR get 4 keys from the Dream Animals, open the path through the yard and enter the Sewers without TOB.
To be able to enter the Sewers without being chased by TOB, KAR first needs to distract or neutralize him. Adding Dream Goat Milk to the Sewer Food.
Give him one of the Stuffed Dream Animals
//todo: more ways to neutralize/distract TOB
//todo: figure out interesting ways to defeat New KARDream Animals (Owl, Tiger, Swan and Fox) reward KAR with a key after finishing a challenge.
Each key leads to a specific locked door in The Corridor.
Behind each door KAR will find a room containing an item that is required to get past one of the rooms in The Yard.
Overview: When KAR reaches the Swan, the Smoker is sitting on a rock near the lake, swearing.
The Smoker constantly mentions putting the Swan on fire.
There's not much to be done here, but when KAR wakes up, the Swan is sitting in the bathtub in the apartment.
The swan screeches if KAR tries to do something in the bathroom.
KAR needs to set the swan on fire.
After that, the lake in Dream Land has burnt away, exposing the lake floor.
KAR can walk down there and pick up a key. The room that the key leads to contains a fire extinguisher, to clear the fire in the yard. The Tiger is surrounded by empty cages.
KAR needs to fill the cages with specific animals.
When the cages are filled, the Tiger gives KAR a key.
The key opens a cage (behind the only open door in The Corridor), a man sits in the cage, hissing like a cat.
When KAR opens the cage the man gives him a GRENADE?
The GRENADE? can be used to blow up the wall in the Yard. The foxes little brother has been kidnapped by the Big Fucker.
Retrieving the little brother
The room contains a gun.
Firing the gun scares away all the birds in the Yard. The Owl is asleep, dreaming of eating something yummy, like a fat rat.
After eating, the owl burps up a key and becomes very angry from waking up.
The owls anger turns the bushes thorny.
The room contains a hedge trimmer to cut through the thorny bushes in the yard.
]]></description><link>chapters/chapter-3.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">CHAPTERS/CHAPTER 3.md</guid><pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2026 14:00:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DREAM LAND]]></title><description><![CDATA[The Dream Land is reachable from Chapter 2 and onwards.
In Chapter # the Paths are available, they are locked off before that. The Hub is the middle section in Dream Land and can be considered pretty safe. The Hub section contains: Where KAR wakes up in his dream and the place to preferably fall asleep and then wake up in the apartment. Falling asleep/waking up outside the bed has consequences.A place of specific knowledge. The person behind the desk knows everything about KAR's daily life. He keeps track of everything. Which is awkward but also useful.
<img alt="BUREAUCRAT.png" src="_images/bureaucrat.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;"><br><img alt="Dream Shop.png" src="_images/dream-shop.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;">A place for KAR to fetch soil and plant dream seeds.At first glance, nothing but a deep puddle, but also Mrs. Octo and Mr. Octo's home.<br>
<img alt="PUDDLE.png" src="_images/puddle.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;">???The six different paths leading from the hub. Each path contains something that prevents KAR from reaching the room at the end of the path. Once there, KAR will have to solve a problem to get the reward (corridor apartment key).
The paths are:This path leads through reed beds and lots of dead and barely living dream fish and ends at the lake with the Swan.<br>
<img alt="Swan Sea.png" src="_images/swan-sea.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;">This path leads through spruce forests to end in the Tiger's clearing<br>
<img alt="TigrClearing.png" src="_images/tigrclearing.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;">This path leads over the meadows to end in the fox potThis path leads up in the big tree and ends in the owl's nest.<br>
<img alt="OWL_PATH.png" src="_images/owl_path.png" target="_self" style="width: 512px; max-width: 100%;">
ALTERNATIVELY:
The path to the owls tree is a maze made of bushes. After the Owl has awoken, the bushes turn thorny and dangerous. This path differs from the others.Nothing but a wet dream at this moment.]]></description><link>location-details/dream-land.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOCATION DETAILS/DREAM LAND.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 15:18:33 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/bureaucrat.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/bureaucrat.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[LOCATIONS]]></title><description><![CDATA[KAR's apartment. Home of TOB for most of the game.
Expands in size as KAR helps TOB gather various materials.
Eventually houses the Tree of Life and a giant Egg. Leads to the Yard, Attic and Basement (property managers office).
The Corridor outside KAR's apartment is a scary place that KAR wants to avoid completely, but sometimes it can be unavoidable to get what KAR needs. High risk/reward area. Multiple descending floors with increasing difficulty to successfully return to his apartment.
Other apartments are inaccessible until KAR manages to get hold of the specific keys in the dream world. The different rooms in the Yard are blocked off, KAR needs to figure out how to unblock them. The Dream Animals have the answers.
In the last of the rooms is the Sewer entrance.
KAR can see the rooms of the Yard through the windows of the apartment.
The first room is full of crows that attack KAR if they walk too close. They can be scared off for good by firing a gun
The second room is full of thorned bushes.
The third room is full of fire.
The forth room is MAYBE blocked by a wall. Home of the Dream Animals, the Bureaucrat, the Shop Keep etc.
More details under LOCATION DETAILSWhere TOB came from.
TOB wants to drag KAR down here. ]]></description><link>locations.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">LOCATIONS.md</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 14:59:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[TigrClearing]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/tigrclearing.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/tigrclearing.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/TigrClearing.png</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:40:34 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/tigrclearing.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/tigrclearing.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[closet]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/closet.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/closet.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/closet.png</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:39:47 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/closet.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/closet.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[KARnEGG]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/karnegg.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/karnegg.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/KARnEGG.png</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:36:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/karnegg.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/karnegg.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Swan Sea]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/swan-sea.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/swan-sea.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/Swan Sea.png</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:33:28 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dream Shop]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/dream-shop.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/dream-shop.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/Dream Shop.png</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Jan 2026 15:33:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="." length="0" type="false"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;.&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[EGG]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/egg.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/egg.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/EGG.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:01:01 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/egg.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/egg.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TREE_OF_LIFE]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/tree_of_life.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/tree_of_life.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/TREE_OF_LIFE.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 14:00:52 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/tree_of_life.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/tree_of_life.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[YONI]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/yoni.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/yoni.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/YONI.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/yoni.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/yoni.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TURD]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/turd.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/turd.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/TURD.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/turd.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/turd.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ROGS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/rogs.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/rogs.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/ROGS.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/rogs.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/rogs.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[PUDDLE]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/puddle.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/puddle.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/PUDDLE.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/puddle.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/puddle.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OWL_PATH]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/owl_path.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/owl_path.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/OWL_PATH.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/owl_path.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/owl_path.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OWL]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/owl.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/owl.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/OWL.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/owl.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/owl.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[NIRD]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/nird.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/nird.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/NIRD.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/nird.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/nird.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MrsOCTO]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/mrsocto.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/mrsocto.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/MrsOCTO.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/mrsocto.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/mrsocto.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kalkan]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/kalkan.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/kalkan.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/Kalkan.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/kalkan.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/kalkan.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[GOATS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/goats.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/goats.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/GOATS.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/goats.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/goats.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FRANK]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/frank.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/frank.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/FRANK.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/frank.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/frank.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FISHES]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/fishes.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/fishes.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/FISHES.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/fishes.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/fishes.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BUREAUCRAT]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/bureaucrat.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/bureaucrat.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/BUREAUCRAT.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/bureaucrat.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/bureaucrat.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ANN]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/ann.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/ann.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/ANN.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/ann.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/ann.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ADMIN]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/admin.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/admin.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/ADMIN.png</guid><pubDate>Mon, 19 Jan 2026 11:24:57 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/admin.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/admin.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TOB]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/tob.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/tob.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/TOB.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/tob.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/tob.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[TIGR]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/tigr.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/tigr.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/TIGR.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/tigr.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/tigr.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SWAN]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/swan.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/swan.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/SWAN.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/swan.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/swan.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SHRIMP]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/shrimp.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/shrimp.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/SHRIMP.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/shrimp.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/shrimp.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SMOKER]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/smoker.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/smoker.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/SMOKER.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/smoker.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/smoker.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SEB]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/seb.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/seb.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/SEB.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/seb.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/seb.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[POMS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/poms.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/poms.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/POMS.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/poms.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/poms.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[RATS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/rats.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/rats.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/RATS.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/rats.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/rats.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[POINTERS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/pointers.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/pointers.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/POINTERS.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/pointers.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/pointers.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OCTO]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/octo.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/octo.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/OCTO.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/octo.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/octo.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[MAN]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/man.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/man.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/MAN.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/man.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/man.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[KITTENS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/kittens.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/kittens.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/KITTENS.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/kittens.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/kittens.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CRYER]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/cryer.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/cryer.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/CRYER.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/cryer.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/cryer.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CROWS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/crows.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/crows.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/CROWS.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/crows.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/crows.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[CATS]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/cats.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/cats.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/CATS.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/cats.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/cats.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BUILDER]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/builder.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/builder.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/BUILDER.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/builder.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/builder.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BKM]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/bkm.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/bkm.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/BKM.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 15:26:07 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/bkm.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/bkm.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[lilFOX]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/lilfox.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/lilfox.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/lilFOX.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/lilfox.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/lilfox.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[STOREOWNER]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/storeowner.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/storeowner.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/STOREOWNER.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/storeowner.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/storeowner.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[SIV]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/siv.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/siv.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/SIV.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/siv.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/siv.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[OLI]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/oli.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/oli.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/OLI.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/oli.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/oli.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[LFU]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/lfu.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/lfu.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/LFU.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/lfu.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/lfu.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[KAR]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/kar.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/kar.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/KAR.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/kar.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/kar.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JANJ]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/janj.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/janj.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/JANJ.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/janj.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/janj.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[JAN]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/jan.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/jan.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/JAN.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/jan.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/jan.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[FOX]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/fox.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/fox.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/FOX.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/fox.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/fox.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[DELI]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/deli.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/deli.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/DELI.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/deli.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/deli.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[BFU]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/bfu.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/bfu.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/BFU.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/bfu.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/bfu.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item><item><title><![CDATA[ABI]]></title><description><![CDATA[<img src="_images/abi.png" target="_self">]]></description><link>_images/abi.html</link><guid isPermaLink="false">_IMAGES/ABI.png</guid><pubDate>Fri, 09 Jan 2026 14:48:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="_images/abi.png" length="0" type="image/png"/><content:encoded>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;_images/abi.png&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;</content:encoded></item></channel></rss>